=A Love Journal= =Episode 8=
= A Love Journal = = الحلقة 8 =
(Dongwu New Century Grand Hotel Huzhou)
(فندق Dongwu New Century Grand Huzhou)
Are you sure
هل أنت واثق
Gu Shen won't come?
لن يأتي قو شين؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I have done the research.
لقد أجريت البحث.
He doesn't come
لا يأتي
to any activity.
لأي نشاط.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
If he comes,
إذا جاء ،
I really don't know how to face him.
أنا حقًا لا أعرف كيف أواجهه.
Well.
نحن سوف.
You haven't told him yet?
لم تخبره بعد؟
It's hard
من الصعب
to explain it to him.
لشرحها له.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
(Main venue of Pushi Design Competition) Why are you willing to come this time?
(المكان الرئيسي لمسابقة تصميم بوشي) لماذا أنت على استعداد للمجيء هذه المرة؟
Didn't you tell me to try going to a new place?
ألم تخبرني أن أحاول الذهاب إلى مكان جديد؟
Something must have happened.
يجب أن يحدث شيء ما.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Don't cover it.
لا تغطيه.
You're
أنت على
a nice guy,
رجل لطيف ،
except that you're a blabbermouth.
إلا أنك ثرثار.
How heartless of you!
يا لك من بلا قلب!
You have to
عليك أن
nail the deal.
اتفق على الصفقة.
But Manager Sun is in charge of the deals with Kangye, right?
لكن المدير صن مسؤول عن الصفقات مع كانجي ، أليس كذلك؟
Don't mention this woman.
لا تذكر هذه المرأة.
She brought her team
أحضرت فريقها
to Liujin Group behind my back.
لمجموعة Liujin خلف ظهري.
I'll get even with her later.
أنا حتى معها في وقت لاحق.
The most important thing now
أهم شيء الآن
is to maintain the relationship with the big clients
هو الحفاظ على العلاقة مع كبار العملاء
she was in charge of.
كانت مسؤولة عن.
Okay, I will go to Ningcheng.
حسنًا ، سأذهب إلى Ningcheng.
If she knows that you are the young mistress of Liujin...
إذا عرفت أنك عشيقة Liujin الشابة ...
A bomb.
قنبلة.
Just wait until that day
فقط انتظر حتى ذلك اليوم
really comes.
يأتي حقا.
You're so carefree.
أنت مرتاح جدا.
But she doesn't know anything.
لكنها لا تعرف أي شيء.
Can you?
هل تستطيع؟
Don't push yourself too hard.
لا تضغط على نفسك بشدة.
(Are you busy?)
(هل أنت مشغول؟)
(Are you going home for dinner tonight?)
(هل ستذهب إلى المنزل لتناول العشاء الليلة؟)
Gu Shen sent me a message
أرسل لي قو شين رسالة
asking if I would go home for dinner.
يسألني إذا كنت سأذهب إلى المنزل لتناول العشاء.
Are you going to be a real couple?
هل ستصبحان زوجين حقيقيين؟
Come on.
هيا.
You know me,
أنت تعرفني،
don't you?
أنت , لا؟
Who knows?
من تعرف؟
Maybe
يمكن
he is the right one for you.
هو الشخص المناسب لك.
I guess
اعتقد
you're the right one for me.
أنت الشخص المناسب لي.
You sexy thing.
أنت شيء مثير.
(Yeah.)
(نعم.)
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
It's great that you can come here.
من الرائع أن تأتي إلى هنا.
Wait for me in the car.
انتظرني في السيارة.